<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kyle Haptonstall</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kyle Haptonstall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.134.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 21:32:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fix Failed Registering Bundle Identifier Error with Automatic Signing in Xcode 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fix-failed-registering-bundle-identifier-error-with-automatic-signing-in-xcode-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 21:32:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fix-failed-registering-bundle-identifier-error-with-automatic-signing-in-xcode-15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;problem&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using Automatic Signing in Xcode 15.4, I received a “Failed Registering Bundle Identifier” error when I went to go add a new Capability for one of my Targets:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;failed-registering-bundle-identifier-error.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the error message states:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The app identifier “…” cannot be registered to your development team because it is not available.&lt;/strong&gt; Change your bundle identifier to a unique string to try again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the app identifier (Bundle Identifier) was already registered under my account in App Store Connect, and signing was previously working prior to adding a new Capability (which updates the Provisioning Profile).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Share Extension with SwiftUI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-a-share-extension-with-swiftui/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 21:32:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-a-share-extension-with-swiftui/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At time of writing, the Share Extension has yet to be given the SwiftUI overhaul that other Target-types have received, so you’ll be met with a UIKit setup and Storyboard interface upon initial creation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re like me and want to leverage SwiftUI wherever possible, this article will show you how to do just that for your Share Extensions 👇&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;share-extension-setup&#34;&gt;Share Extension Setup&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sections below will walk you through setting up a brand new Share Extension in your app. If you’ve already got one setup, feel free to jump down to SwiftUI Conversion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Repository of Xcode Code Snippets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-a-repository-of-xcode-code-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:32:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-a-repository-of-xcode-code-snippets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This post will outline a process of checking Xcode Code Snippets into source control in order to build out a library of snippets you can easily import on new machines or take with you to new companies. (You can also use this to create a shared library of snippets within a development team.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won’t go over how to create and use code snippets &lt;em&gt;within&lt;/em&gt; Xcode, but if you’d like a refresher, check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://sarunw.com/posts/how-to-create-code-snippets-in-xcode/&#34;&gt;this post by Sarun&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Static Site in Swift using Ignite and GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-a-static-site-in-swift-using-ignite-and-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 21:32:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-a-static-site-in-swift-using-ignite-and-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently decided to update my personal home page (a simple one-page HTML site using Jekyll) to try out Ignite, as I’d much prefer to maintain a Swift package over working directly with HTML.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/twostraws/Ignite&#34;&gt;Ignite&lt;/a&gt; is an open-source static site builder for Swift developers, created by &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/twostraws&#34;&gt;Paul Hudson&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While working with Ignite is fairly straightforward, and there are plenty of excellent examples provided in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/twostraws/IgniteSamples&#34;&gt;IgniteSamples&lt;/a&gt; repo, I ran into a couple speed bumps deploying via &lt;a href=&#34;https://pages.github.com&#34;&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
