<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>One Byte at a Time</title>
    <description>I&#39;m Kyle, a junior Computer Science major, available for hire! 
</description>
    <link>http://khaptonstall.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://khaptonstall.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 13:00:14 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 13:00:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up and Running</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Hello World!&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s about time I got a site up and running (thank you GitHub).I think I can say I&amp;#39;ve done more before noon than the average college kid on a Saturday morning. I&amp;#39;ll use my first post for a deeper introduction of myself. I&amp;#39;m Kyle, a junior CompSci major with a Math minor, set to graduate from Monmouth College in 2016. I find myself very busy, being not only a student, but also a soldier in the U.S. Army Reserve (hooah!), member of the marching and concert bands at school, member of the Sigma Phi Epsilon, IL Gamma Chapter, and President and Founder of my Student Chapter of the ACM. If only there was an app that gave me more time in the day! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside of classes I enjoy taking on various projects and learning new ideas. With the time I manage to find, I have tought myself several languages, such as Python, HTML, CSS, Swift, Octave, and Mathematica. I&amp;#39;ve also recently transitioned to an Apple centered life, and in doing so have learned how to work Xcode and program iOS apps. I&amp;#39;m currently working on a project to ease the mess of communication and flyers in your face that is Fraternity/Sorority rush week. While working on development, I have also picked up knowledge of tools and third-party libraries such as Facebook SDK and Parse for databases. Plans are to launch via Apple App Store before Fall 2015, and work on an Android version for Spring 2016. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My hopes for my blog/website is to continue with updates of projects, research, and a little bit of life. I will probably move my blog from my previous summer&amp;#39;s research on Android GUI Software Testing over from blogger to here in one giant post, just for archival reasons. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Kyle&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 06:39:56 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://khaptonstall.github.io/jekyll/update/2015/04/18/up-and-running.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://khaptonstall.github.io/jekyll/update/2015/04/18/up-and-running.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
